<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Mejin&#039;s Open Table</title>
      <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Mejin&#039;s Open Table</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Cadabear</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Monsters/Cadabear</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Monsters/Cadabear</guid>
    <description> Cadabears are a relatively recently discovered form of undead. The cadabear is more than an undead bear, it is heartier overall and relies on smell and sound rather than sight.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:13:53 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Vulpine Marker</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Resources/New-Items/Vulpine-Marker</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Resources/New-Items/Vulpine-Marker</guid>
    <description>Overview A socketable item with 1 charge. A subtle section of a vulpine inkling that it used when tracking its prey. When this item is socketed into a magic item it can spend its charge to cast Hunters Mark as a bonus action.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 01:10:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Vulpine Inkling</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Monsters/Vulpine-Inkling</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Monsters/Vulpine-Inkling</guid>
    <description> Vulpine inklings appear as a fox made out of living ink and able to manipulate their form with between that of a puddle and that of a fox. While they do hunt for food, they often hide from creatures larger than themselves, but will fight if cornered.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:09:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Sudsee</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Sudsee</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Sudsee</guid>
    <description>Overview A notable lake bound fishing and farming village, Sudsee has a lot of trade with Bergstadt. The town itself houses a simple community with a single tavern, an elected mayor, and only enough spears to arm those capable of fighting.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 01:57:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Kleihafen</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Kleihafen</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Kleihafen</guid>
    <description>Overview Known for the Temple of the Five, Kleihafen is a popular pilgrimage spot. The town is also a major port, so goods and people regularly arrive.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 01:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Shafedorf</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Shafedorf</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Shafedorf</guid>
    <description>Overview A herding town that has been growing as of late, which has led to good stone being a scarce resource, and often trades with Flusstadt to get its hands on some ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:54:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dimal Barport</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Characters/Minor-NPCs/Dimal-Barport</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Characters/Minor-NPCs/Dimal-Barport</guid>
    <description>Dimal was an apprentice wizard at the Zweiflus Grand Library. After he had been studying there for some time, Dimal made off with thousands of gold worth of books on magic, killing 5 people in his escape.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Ostwald</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Ostwald</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Ostwald</guid>
    <description>Overview A lumber town in the southern Ausfallen region, Ostwald is known for its high quality wood working, its festivals, and its colorful people. Ostwalds population is largely Beast-Folk, and the city celebrates its fey origins with riddle championships, a culture of flower arrangements, and a tradition of story telling.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Sudhafen</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Sudhafen</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Sudhafen</guid>
    <description>Overview A vibrant port city, Sudhafen has a colorful market with trade from all over the coast, travel to distant islands, and many rare goods. Run by a committee elected by the people, Sudhafen is a safe town.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:37:52 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mauerinhugeln</title>
    <link>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Mauerinhugeln</link>
    <guid>https://www.mejinsopentable.com/Lore/Locations/Cities-and-Towns/Mauerinhugeln</guid>
    <description>Overview Beginning its life as a castle built to house and train the fledgling Watchmen, Mauerinhugeln gathered tradesmen to itself to support its growth ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:45 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>